Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature was hurt during
the production of this show.
Malhun Hatun...
I'll have a child, won't I?
I'll give you a child.
Thank you my Lord.
Thank you my Lord...
... you answered my pray.
You didn't leave me without a child.
Malhun Hatun.
You fulfilled my longing.
You brought heaven to my tent.
Now, tell me.
You can wish anything from me.
My happiness is seeing you happy.
Even more, If you give birth
to a son...
He'll be a heir of mine.
Hay Masha Allah (praise be).
Can I come in?
Come.
Bala.
I'll have a child.
This is good news for all of us.
It is.
Thank Lord.
Excuse me, my Bey.
Of course.
Osman Bey.
This must be between us for now.
We need to be sure about our child's
health condition first.
We shouldn't raise people's hopes
for nothing.
Allah forbid. Allah forbid.
But you are right.
You shall rest.
Take care of yourself and our child.
And you shall make your wish.
We shall not tell anyone.
I'll talk to the healer Hatun.
Can we come in?
Come.
From now on...
You must take a good care of
Malhun Hatun.
Do not let her work.
Do not upset her.
- As you command, my Bey.
- Eyvallah (thank you).
Eyvallah.
May Allah bless you.
My Hanım, are you okay?
I am fine, Alaca.
Good news, Bala.
Good news.
Good news to you, Osman Bey.
What are you waiting for, Osman Bey?
Won't you notify your tribe?
Not now.
The tribe should not know it at
the moment.
Also Malhun Hatun wants to be sure
the baby is healthy.
She is right.
- She is right.
- Yes.
We shall not excite the tribe.
Well thought, my Osman.
It is wise to hide it until you are sure.
Right.
Bala?
What is wrong with Malhun Hatun?
She is good, Gonca.
She felt dizzy a little.
She needs a rest.
Salam Alaikum.
(peace be upon you).
Alaikum salam.
(you too)
My brothers and sisters are coming
from Germiyan Land, Master Davut.
They are willing to fight on Osman Bey's
side like me.
Masha Allah(praise be!)
This is what we call good news.
Did you hear, Boran Alp?
A valiant joined our tribe and paved the
way for one thousand valiants, Master Davut.
Eyvallah(thank you) brother Boran.
They can come, but being Osman Bey's Alp
is not something easy.
Novice people just slow us down,
Turan Alp.
- Excuse me Master Davut.
- Eyvallah (okay) my valiant.
- Excuse me too, Master Davut.
- Eyvallah my valiant.
Davut Bey, did I do something wrong
to Goktug?
Brother, you are doing wrong.
You forgot too soon, Boran. A betrayer
came out of the refrugees recently.
What do you expect me to do? Should I give
their men in Osman Bey's order right away?
Do you think I don't care about Osman
Bey's security, brother?
If you do, you need to be cautious.
Brother, this shouldn't be an attitude
of Osman Bey's Alp.
This is inappropriate.
Goktug, stop being selfish.
I have works to do.
You can go continue your chat with Turan.
What is this all pomegranate thing?
I saw pomegranate trees portrayed in...
the both sides of the window in
the south wall of...
Mevalana's shrine.
It was also portrayed in the tombstone.
Glazed china of Kubadabad.
This is pomegranate branches you see
right here which symbolise...
heaven and the eternal life.
Pomegranate was mentioned in
Quran many times.
It is the fruit of heaven.
Pomegranate symbolises earth. The grains
in it symbolises people.
The membrane among the grains
symbolises the differences among people.
It shows that we are one even though
there are differences.
In conclusion, pomegranate is the image
of eternal life and power.
Power.
Turks and power.
Your power is like this pomegranate
I squish in my hand...
Sultan Mesut.
Let's talk about the tax.
My Sultan, we recieved a letter from
Osman Bey.
Osman Bey will visit me.
Governors stated they wouldn't
pay tax first.
Now, Osman is coming.
Let's see what's behind this.
It was wise to end your hostility
with Osman Bey.
Byzantine is behind this is you wonder.
Byzantine can't oppose me.
I will support Osman Bey if he fights
against Byzantine.
I have no doubt.
Osman's worth is measured by his enemy.
Ominous infidel!
I apologize, my Sultan.
We have more important issues
than this ominous man.
I hear the footsteps of a huge war that
we will involve too.
I'll give you a child.
Thank Lord.
Can I come in Osman Bey?
Come brother!
I'll go to Konya tomorrow.
I have to talk to Sultan
about the war.
Now it's Nicola's turn after Togay,
inshallah. (if Allah permits.)
I hope you bring good news from
Konya, Osman Bey.
Inshallah brother,
inshallah(if Allah permits)
Turanalp is excited.
He has news.
- He is waiting for your permission.
- He shall not wait. Summon him.
Turanalp!
My Bey.
Tell me what the important news is.
I have Ghazi brothers who want to come
from Germiyan and fight by your side.
They are waiting for your permission.
Masha Allah (praise be)
So, do you...
vouch for them?
Their swords are sharp, their hearts
are clean, their intention is good.
They are living for war, they are
waiting for shahada.
How holy is that!
I have permission.
Let them come.
- They shall join.
- We will not let you down my Bey.
We shall not let you down,
you shall not either.
May Allah gather us up in the war.
Amin.
We can't trust Osman.
Sultan is supporting Osman.
We'll take our steps according to this.
Let Sultan think our hostility with
Osman ended.
Is it time to pay him for abducting Togay
and seizing our gold?
Do not doubt, Borucu.
do not doubt.
Brother, take care of yourself in Konya.
You can't know anyone in Konya.
Vali Yargucu knows what happened to Togay
and his taxes are paid by Nicola.
Don't worry, brother.
Osman Bey, is there something you hide?
What is that about brother?
Are you excited for the upcoming war?
I don't think so.
Are you excited for the news
Turan Alp brought?
I don't think so.
There must be something else.
What can I hide from you, brother?
Osman Bey, you can hide, you can tell.
It's up to you, but you can't convince
me to believe that there is nothing.
So tell me...
What can...
make your brother so happy?
What can excite me more than the war?
- Brother?
- Yes.
Is my brother being a father?
I will be a father!
What a surprise!
Congratulations, brother,
Congratulations.
What are we waiting for, brother? Let's
notify everybody! Come here.
We'll have a ceremony.
We'll have a ceremony right away.
We'll feed the poors.
Wait a second, brother.
We need to be sure about my child's health
first. We can have a ceremony later.
I'll go to Konya first. Then we can
do whatever you want!
So, we'll hide. You are right, brother.
We'll hide.
How are we going to manage that, Osman?
Ayse will understand, I know it.
However, I'll shut my mouth.
I swear I'll shut my mouth brother.
Masha Allah (praise be).
Okay then.
I will leave Osman Bey.
I'll go now. Osman, I need to get out
of the tent, ride my horse.
I cannot fit in here.
I am leaving Osman Bey.
Take care of yourself.
Another wolf-faced is coming, huh?
Right.
Mashallah (praise be)
See you later.
Bala.
I'll go to Konya tomorrow.
I have an important issue to talk to
Sultan.
I want you to know something before
you leave.
What is that?
You don't have to hide your happiness,
my Osman.
I know how happy you are to fulfill
your longing for a child...
to do the bequest of Ertugrul Ghazi.
I heard how happy your voice was...
while talking to your brother Gunduz.
My Bey, you are happy.
You deserved it.
Do not hide it.
Even more...
involve me in this happiness.
My Bala...
Happiness without you is not
the real happiness for me.
Just picked these.
I chose the sweetest ones for you.
Do you grow only apple?
Yes, only apple.
Do you wish anyting else.
Do you know pomegranate.
I know, of course.
But I don't grow it in my garden.
Can you find any?
It is a winter fruit, Malhun Hatun?
You can't find it in summer.
Yes, true. It would be awesome
if we had some though.
Take a good care of Malhun Hatun
from now on. Do not let her work.
Do not upset her.
I'll try to find.
It's going to be hard.
Just check.
Maybe somebody brought it to Sogut.
I'll check it.
Welcome my Bey.
Malhun Hatun.
My travel is to Konya.
But my mind is here.
I wanted you to know.
Take your mind with you, Osman Bey.
You shall leave your heart here.
I can't sleep.
My heart is bumping so strong that
it'll thurst through my breast.
Both my mind and heart is here
with my child.
You shall leave, Osman Bey.
Do not worry about us.
I'll protect my body until that
glorious day comes and...
you hold your baby.
I will remember I carry two lives
in one body.
May Allah bless you.
Osman Bey.
We'll wait for your return with
our child.
Mashallah (praise be).
Kill them!
He is not Turk, idiot!
Commander Ducas.
He came in advance to examine.
What I understand is...
we don't need enemy...
while you are here.
Forgive us, Commander Ducas.
I now understand better how Nicola's
soldiers were...
slaughtered by Osman like pigs!
Do not forget we are here to cover
Nicola's faults...
not to only clear Turks in Bitinya.
Our mission is not easy.
I am here to congratulate.
Welcome.
Here...
Thank you.
Your visit made me happy.
We have a good news.
We have been waiting for it.
May Allah bless you.
You satisfied us.
We'll wait for a while, then
we'll notify the tribe inshallah.
Inshallah (if Allah permits).
- Take it.
- Thank you.
Bala Hatun.
These socks are beautiful!
I am very happy to take them.
I stitched them myself for our
child with Osman Bey.
However...
They were destined for your child.
And you are giving them to me now?
I'll be happy if you clothe your child
with these.
After all, it's my Osman's child.
Also...
I will be a kind of mother.
Of course you will be.
You will be.
If this is going to relieve you a bit...
Of course you are going to be...
like a mother.
Thank you.
I'll leave.
I wish we met in another way.
We could have been a good couple.
But we didn't.
This is our destiny.
Welcome Ducas.
The unfailing warrior of Ceasar...
Nicola.
Ceaser it was, right?
You were a fan of his wars when
you were young.
Great leader, great commander.
I always respected your memory,
Ducas.
There is no Ceaser in the battlefield.
We are.
Are we?
I damaged Turks a lot, Ducas.
I stopped their grow.
Now it is time to get rid of them.
I don't have time for empty talk, Nciola.
Start working now.
We'll go to food house to welcome the
families coming from Germiyan.
I'll join you when I'm done with this.
I want to participate in this charity.
One must not run away from charity,
Ayse Hatun. Thank you.
Well said.
- Have a nice day.
- Thank you Zoe.
Why are you staring?
I am looking at the Osman Bey's hatun
who washed the clothes.
These are Osman Bey's. I can't
let anyone else do it.
Where are you going?
I need to go Sogut, Bala Hatun.
I need to visit the woofer.
Okay then, go.
Have a nice day.
We believe you won't disrespect our Sultan,
Osman Bey.
Our Sultan deserves respect not because
of your words...
but because of his good intentions.
Don't worry, Perdadar Efendi (Bey).
Here you go.
The doors!
Kayı Bey Ertugrul Ghazi's son Osman Bey.
- Welcome, Osman Bey.
- Thank you my Sultan.
You got rid of Togay thanks to the
information I gave you.
Thanks to you...
I dealt with not only Togay,
but also Byzantine's game.
According to the information I recieved,
they'll attack us with a...
huge army under Emperor's order.
I thought so.
Emperor send a messenger.
His governors rejected paying
tax to Seljuqs.
A Macedonian commander will be
leading the army. His name is Dukas.
Dukas.
He destroyed my army earlier.
He is dangerous and brave.
He hates Turks more than Mongols.
What is the source of your
information, Osman Bey?
My Sultan.
The walls of the palace are thin, I heard.
You can trust my source.
Then, Byzantine aims Seljuqs...
not you.
They aim me.
My army will be ready.
I'll be leading my army.
You shall get ready for the war
with your Ghazis.
My Sultan, we don't need to get
ready for war. We already are.
May Allah help you all, Osman Bey.
My Sultan.
- My Bey.
- Let's go.
Are the soldiers ready?
The best, the most savage ones
are ready, Vali Yargucu.
Nice.
So, does this Osman have no flaw?
He does.
He has a big flaw.
Osman is in love.
In love?
With whom?
With his wife.
With Bala.
How can it be a flaw that a man
is in love with his wife, Nicola?
What can we do with this info?
Bala can't give birth.
Osman didn't want to marry anyone
else despite of this fact.
This shows he has a flaw.
He got rid of his flaw
by marrying Malhun Hatun.
Fortunately, I made my move to see
his other flaws.
I'll introduce you to my spy
in Kayı Tribe.
Doors!
Zoe.
Commander Dukas.
My spy in Kayı tribe.
So you managed to get in Kayı
tribe.
You brought important news with
you after your absence...
right Zoe?
I have a crucial news for you.
Osman Bey's Hatun
Malhun Hatun...
is pregnant.
Zoe.
You are close to Malhun Hatun, right?
I am her servant.
While our armies crush Osman's alps...
Kayı tribe will recieve a bad news.
Zoe.
Go.
Do what you need to do.
Gunduz Bey is approaching!
Welcome to Kayı tent, valiants!
Thank you my Bey!
Mashallah (praise be).
- Sheik Edebali is approaching!
- Sheik Edebali is coming.
- Welcome valiants.
- Thank you my Sheik.
Akca, take them to food house.
Let them eat.
Bala Hatun is ready there, my Sheik.
We are ready.
Our boilers are boiling.
We can take them right now, my Sheik.
Welcome, you brought us goodness.
You are welcomed here.
It is a honor to host you.
My Sheik, we heard Kayı Hatuns are
fighters too.
Bala Hatun, Gonca Hatun, Aygül Hatun.
We heard of them.
We want to fight too.
What do you say, Gündüz Bey?
Male lion and female lion are
the same, they are one, my Sheik.
We are all sons and daughters of
Oghuz Khan. We love to fight!
I am hungry, uncle.
Mashallah (praise be)
Come here, my valiant.
Let's go!
What are you waiting for?
Alps! Here is the community of Kayi.
Here is the case we are going
to die for.
Let's go.
Goktug.
I don't want it, thanks.
Goktug, don't push it. Come on brother.
Goktug.
- Come here.
- Yes my bey.
What is the problem...
between you and Boran?
What happened when I was at palace?
Tell me.
Saltug Alp is coming!
My Bey, it's Mongols.
They are crowded.
Alps!
Relax.
But be cautious too.
- Goktug.
- Yes my Bey.
Let them come.
- Boran.
- Yes my Bey.
- You know what to do.
- I do, my Bey.
Okay.
Aykurt, Saltug.
Let's go Alps!
Alps!
Wait for my sign. We'll wait for them
to come. Be careful.
Come on.
Did Yargucu send you_
Get up and kneel!
What did Yargucu say?
Did he told you to ask me to kneel,
that I'd accept it?
I said kneel!
If you came here to make me kneel.
Then...
Watch out for your knees.
Kill them all!
Goktug.
- You are late, brother.
- No offense, brother.
I'll be quicker next time.
- Eyvallah Eyvallah (thank you)
- Keep on!
Osman Bey, forgive my life.
Forgive my life.
Not you, not Yargucu...
Even Geyhatu came...
Even Genghis Khan got out of
his tomb and came here...
Nobody could make me kneel.
You'll fail Osman.
You'll fail.
Ertugrul Ghazi's son Osman Bey
has always a plan.
However, the real plan is Allah's plan.
From now on, I shall not postpone
Allah's plan for you.
Dark Osman shall perform.
My Bey, what did these dogs want from us?
Our rebellion offended Yargucu.
Tell me, what is going on between you?
I was a bit frustrated, but my valiant
brother made it all right.
My brother.
- My Goktug.
- Mashallah (praise be).
A valiant does not get hurt
by enemy's sword.
He gets hurt by his
friend's smack.
Eyvallah my Bey,
I am happy to...
make everything like they
were used to be.
See the roots of a tree to check
if it's good...
hear a valiant's words to check
if he's good.
Praise you together!
Eyvallah (thank you) my Bey.
Gather up Alps!
We are going to the tribe.
It's time to destroy the
enemy with Turk's smack!
Let's go!
- May Allah Bless you.
- May Allah bless you.
Can you add more? I'll take it to my
children.
Not only Ghazis, but also their families
are coming now, Bala Hatun.
Sogut will be crowded. The comers will
be fruitful I hope.
I hope so.
Bala, we are at ease now.
I'll go to the woofer if you excuse me.
Of course Gonca.
We'll handle the rest.
Thank you.
Enjoy your mela.
Look how beautiful she is, Ayse Hatun!
Mashallah (praise be)
She is a beauty.
- Thank you.
- Masha Allah (praise be).
You are the beauty, Bala Hatun.
We've alwasy wondered who Osman
Bey's Hatun is.
Mashallah. You are beautiful.
Thank you.
I've heard that
Ghazi's came from Germiyan.
-I wanted to see if I can help.
-Welcome, Malhun Hatun.
I've heard that
Ghazi's came from Germiyan.
-I wanted to see if I can help.
-Welcome, Malhun Hatun.
Welcome. Come.
You look curious.
Let me help you.
I'm Kızılbeyoğlu Umur Bey's
daughter...
Osman Bey's wife, Malhun Hatun.
Osman Bey is very lucky.
Come to me when you are in need.
Thank you.
Allah bless you.
-Good day.
-Welcome, Gonca Hatun.
-Thank you. Are the fabric here?
-Yes.
Thank you.
Are you pleased with the fabric
I provided for the wedding?
Zoey would come here today.
She is Malhun Hatun's helper.
You should've asked her instead.
-Did she not come?
-I was here the whole day.
She didn't come.
Oh, bully... Oh, bully... Come and get me.
Ah, boys...
Who are you?
What do you want from me?
Boys, right?
Even a hoar like you talk of them.
What do you want from me, I said!
You sneaked in like a snake!
Cut it short, hoar.
I came for a cure.
-What cure?
-There is a woman burdened by a bully.
I want to take off her burden.
I want to take it off in a way that...
neither she nor her husband
will know it.
What are you saying?
Leave here!
-I don't want anyone to get suspicious.
-Get out, I say!
It shouldn't happen as soon as
she drinks the poison.
It should kill the child
in her belly.
I want her to rot while she crawls
from the loss of her child.
Do you understand?
And I brought you Nikola's regards.
-Why didn't you say before?
-I wanted to see if you are quiet.
I'm quiet as a mute.
And my venom is deadlier
than a snake. But...
-But what?
-You need to wait for that poison.
It should wait like wine for her
to enjoy it.
Eat, my lions, eat.
You fought well.
We beat them well.
Cerkutay, fill your stomach.
The great battle is soon.
The sultan promised Osman Bey.
He will send an army.
Cerkutay, what are you thinking?
The great battle will have
great spoils.
Cerkutay, were you this interested
in the spoils?
Without spoils, there is no dowry.
Without dowry, there is no wedding.
Without wedding, it's no good.
Without battle, there are no spoils.
What would you do without the battle?
It would be easier for
the old Cerkutay.
But nevermind, let's not talk about
the old Cerkutay in Bamsı Bey's tent.
Allah will feed everyone.
Indeed, indeed. But without battle,
you would never marry.
Boran Alp is married.
What about you?
How will you marry Zoey?
Zoey? What Zoey?
Listen to me, save some money.
Weddings are expensive.
Yeah.
-Bala.
-My bey.
What were you doing? Tell me.
What did you do at Söğüt?
-Was the food enough for the hungry?
-Thank Allah, it was enough.
-Everyone is taken care of.
-Mashallah. Mashallah.
Now, you are getting more jobs and
more burden.
Thank Malhun Hatun.
She came there too.
What did she do?
-She came to Söğüt?
-She introduced herself to the people.
Then, she handed out food
with us.
The table is ready, my bey.
I cooked the food you like.
Thank you, Bala. Thank you.
I should check Malhun Hatun.
Then, I'll come and we'll eat.
As you want, my bey.
-Welcome, Osman Bey.
-Malhun Hatun?
-You made preparation.
-I have.
I told you. You'll always see a smiling
face and a table at the ready.
-I told you to not tire yourself.
-I didn't mount a horse and went to battle.
It's just a table. Come.
I'm not hungry. I came to ask
if you are alright.
Will you stay that short?
If you are alright--
You don't want me to leave, right?
Don't feel forced, Osman Bey.
I can eat alone.
Are you alright?
Come and sit.
Sit here.
I'm alright, Osman Bey.
I'm alright. Don't worry.
Malhun Hatun, why are you making
preparations like this?
Let Alaca Hatun do it from now on.
Drink this now.
You are right, Osman Bey. I should
be more careful.
-Are you any better?
-I'm alright, Osman Bey.
Now, I'm not going anywhere.
I'm here, with you.
Don't tire yourself and
don't make yourself sad.
Come on. Come on, eat.
With the name of Allah.
Go on, come on.
Eat, eat, come on.
With the name of Allah.
May it be easy, Gonca Hatun.
Have you done your shopping
at Söğüt?
All the fabric was so good. I found
everything I was looking for.
Good.
What's wrong, Gonca?
Why are you worried?
I've talked to Zoey. She told me that
she bought fabric from Söğüt.
-So, what's wrong with that?
-Bala, I was there too.
Zoey never went there.
She must be doing something.
I think it's better if you talk to
Malhun Hatun about this.
Let's not accuse her now.
Maybe it has an explanation.
Also, Malhun Hatun might misunderstand it.
She might think that we don't
want her in the tribe.
What will we do, then?
Keep your eyes on her.
When we make sure...
-I'll talk to Malhun Hatun.
-As you wish, Bala.
-May it be easy.
-Thank you.
A momento from Kutamışoğlu Süleyman
Shah.
Osman Bey deserves it.
Mashallah.
When the order came from
Constantinople...
all the lords united...
and Sultan Mesud made his
decision.
He thought that all the preperations
were against him.
And for this reason, he'll come personally
with his army.
Sultan Mesud will come personally, huh?
Sultan Mesud wants you to stand with
us in this battle.
This is a matter of life and death,
Osman Bey.
When will we stand with you
if not today?
Our sultan will come from Konya and
we'll stay idle? Is that possible?
Of course not! All Turkmen beys
love jihad!
When the swords start to strike
the shields...
they can't keep anyone in their tents.
Yarhisar, Bilecik...
İnegöl, Söğüt...
Firstly, we need to protect that line.
-This line will be bolstered, sir.
-If Turks...
pass this line...
their next target will be the heart of
Bhytinia, İznik.
We won't let them have this dream.
I'm listening, Commander Dukas.
After forming the line and
protecting ourselves...
from İnegöl border to
Germian border...
we'll push Turks to the east with
never-ending attacks.
Their herds, goods, whatever they have...
we'll fight to make them run away
without thinking to take anything with them!
We'll make them migrate to where
they came.
Until they run back to the
hell they came from!
This is it. This is the great battle
we have been waiting for.
Your words reminded me of the Helenic
pride that I've forgotten.
Really bold words.
You amazed us, Commander Dukas.
Victory will be ours!
According to our intelligence, Nikola
is forming a defensive line.
That will take two weeks at least.
In the meantime, Dukas will reach
İnegöl with his army.
15 days will be enough for us to prepare.
You will face their defensive line.
You'll follow the enemy and gather
information.
When the night falls,
send good warriors to the other side...
and take some captives.
If we can make them talk, then we'll
find out about their plans.
But, Umur Bey...
you have the biggest responsibiltiy.
You'll keep an eye around Domaniç
Our claws will be upon them until
the battle starts.
And when it begins, we'll be upon
them with 'Allahu Akbar's!
-Don't worry, Osman Bey.
-Alright, alright, Umur Bey.
My alps are ready for any mission
you'll give, Osman Bey.
Don't worry about it's being
difficult, Osman Bey.
We'll make home from
whatever we get.
All the borders will be our home and
all the ghazis are our alps.
Thank you, my bey.
Alps who came from Germiyan
has the same sense.
Turan Alp will prepare
the alps for the battle.
-As you order, my bey.
-Thank you, thank you, Turan Alp.
My beys, my ghazis...
the time is coming,
the enemy is gathering.
Among all the battles that have
come...
this will be the greatest.
The eyes of our ghazi ancestors
will be upon us.
I'll take İznik for the Turks.
This dagger that belonged
to the great sultan...
our ghazi ancestor, Kutalmışoğlu
Süleyman Shah...
should remind you of our centuries
old cause.
For the memory of all the warriors
who took these lands for us.
Allahu Akbar!
Victory belongs to those who have faith.
Allahu Akbar.
Around Domaniç
15 days later
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam, Osman Bey.
-You are just in time, Osman Bey.
-How many are they?
-Around 40.
-They aren't Nikola's soldiers.
-Must be the vanguard.
-Let's be quick.
-Alps! Stay here.
-Alright, my bey.
They chose a good spot.
I've been personally watching...
their moves in the last
three days.
Thank you, Umur Bey.
Thank you.
-Found anyhing?
-As you said...
they must be the vanguard.
Brother, what do you think?
Their intention will be to meet
with the main army.
-This is a secret place.
-If so, what will be their target?
Lately, the intensity among
the soldiers...
grew around Domaniç
I say that we should attack and
end them here.
Not now, Umut Bey.
Not now.
What's on your mind, Osman Bey?
Dukas' army isn't here yet.
Watch every step they take,
Umur Bey.
Alright.
The armies of Yaso and the other
lords will wait here for your orders.
It will take half a day to reach.
Dear Dukas, welcome.
Our defensive line is almost ready.
Tomorrow, we'll hurt Osman before
the great battle.
Why tomorrow, Dukas?
-Don't tell me the soldiers aren't ready.
-We are ready. Why tomorrow?
Osman knows you very well.
He can guess your moves.
-You fought a lot.
-He doesn't know Commander Dukas.
-The vanguard will hit him good.
-So?
Before my army reaches here, I'll
blur his mind with this attack.
The information my spies bring
me shows everything.
Osman Bey positioned his alps
all the way.
-They change positions and ambush.
-They are ambushing ghosts.
-They don't know my numbers.
-Like a blind eagle.
Now is the time to hit a small
but effective blow.
-Good.
-Nikola, finish preperations.
Athnos, come with me.
Let's see the defensive line together.
-How long will we endure this insolence?
-Shh...
A little bit longer.
Lord Leo is still not here.
If he is exposed...
Then, Nikola will kill him without
blinking an eye.
Lord Leo!
I'm glad to see you. We were afraid
something happened.
If you can't stop Nikola and Dukas,
much worse will happen to me.
I'm surrounded by Nikola's spies.
It was difficult to come
here, Osman Bey.
-Any news?
-Unfortunately, yes.
I heard from Lord Athnos that...
Nikola and Dukas are planning to
attack Domaniç
He tried me to convince joining
the battle.
Just as we guessed.
Tomorrow, they'll move for the attack.
Our intelligence says that the attack
will be around Domaniç
We proved it with your words.
-Should we inform other beys?
-Now is the time.
-Everyone should be ready for battle.
-Alright.
-Göktuğ?
-Yes, brother.
-There is something off with you. Tell me.
-No, brother.
Göktuğ, tell me.
Brother, I bought this at Konya.
For Zoey.
But I couldn't give it to her.
I want to give it to her tomorrow,
before going to battle.
-But you don't have the courage.
-Brother, you know me.
I can charge into an army.
But when it's about love, I don't know
what to do.
Brother, a ghazi shouldn't
look behind.
-Go and tell her.
-How, brother? How?
Brother, do you want me to go and
tell? What do you want?
-I'll ask something if you won't get mad.
-I won't. Ask away.
Brother, tell me. How did you speak
to my Gonca sister?
Tell me. Show me a way!
Now, firstly tell me.
Does the girl love you too?
I don't know brother.
But when I look into her eyes, I find
myself lost.
Look, brother.
Alp's heart doesn't make his tongue
speak, but his arms.
If the girl loves you...
she'll understand not what you say,
but what you feel.
Not what you are able to express
but what you aren't, Göktuğ.
Brother, face her.
And tell everything you want.
Thank you, brother.
Thank you.
I should leave then.
-Good night, Gonca sister.
-Thank you.
What's wrong with Göktuğ?
He has a trouble with
no cure, Gonca.
What is it?
My brother is in love.
God bless you.
Why would they be helpless?
They can marry and it will be solved.
-Gonca.
-Yes.
Does the fire of love end when you marry?
I don't know. You tell me.
Does it?
I wish I was with you in this war,
fighting side by side.
You gave me the greatest
evangel!
And now, you are carrying the
most valuable one.
This is more valuable than the battle.
If Allah blesses me with
a son...
if I have a son...
if I'm destined to fight side
by side with my son...
You will be, Osman.
You will.
Inshallah.
After having your heir...
will you come to this tent...
and still care for me?
Help me, my Allah.
Come on, Göktuğ.
With the name of Allah. Come on.
Göktuğ.
We meet a lot.
Is this a coincidence?
It's not a coincidence.
I know you walk here every morning.
Are you watching me, Göktuğ Alp?
I don't have bad intentions. You know,
in spring, you see pretty flowers.
You want to look at them. You don't have
bad intentions. You like to see nice things.
Same as this.
I wanted to buy it when I saw it.
I opened the gate of Kulucahisar,
I got shot with arrows many times.
But the gates of my heart...
was opened by you.
By the look of you, you are afraid
of getting shot again.
I'm not afraid of the arrows of
the enemy but...
the words of your mouth.
You should know.
Where are you going?
To my bey, for duty.
Göktuğ.
I'll be awaiting your return.
Thank Allah.
Now is the time.
What's wrong, Bala?
Do you doubt the victory?
When have you lost a battle after
getting betrayed, Osman?
-I would never doubt you.
-Not at all. Not at all.
I doubt us, but not you.
That was a blade wound.
Stop torturing yourself, Bala.
Don't wound me when I'm going
to battle.
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come in.
-My bey, your alps are awaiting orders.
-Mount. I'm coming.
May Allah sharpen your sword, Osman Bey.
Break the wings of the heathens.
I await your victory.
This is what I want to hear from you.
-May Allah protect you.
-You too, Osman Bey.
This is your day, Dukas.
And the word is yours.
We formed our defensive line.
We'll kick the Turks out of our
invaded lands!
Until our army comes from Macedonia,
we'll play a bloody game.
We'll lure them into our trap!
Are you ready to destroy the Turks?
Are you ready for victory?
Victory!
-Bala.
-Gonca.
I followed Zoey. She left the
tribe today.
I followed her to Söğüt.
But...
She removed her trace in side alleys.
She removed her trace, huh?
-So, it's certain now?
-I'm sure, Bala.
My bey, Byzantine dogs were seen
at Karaçam Valley.
Around the place that Umur Bey
noticed. They'll attack the villages nearby.
-Turan, Saltuk.
-My bey.
-Inform the alps.
-As you order, my bey.
-You know what to do.
-Yes, my bey.
Now is the time for battle!
Come on!
It's not as big as we thought.
What are you thinking, Osman Bey.
Neither Nikola nor Ducas
are with them.
What will we do, Osman Bey?
Firstly, we'll take care of them.
Show no mercy.
Umur Bey, you will attack from the
rear with your alps.
Turan Alp will aid you with his alps.
Alps, come on.
May Allah bless our efforts.
Battle formation!
-God damn it! How could that happen?
-Don't you understand?
Dukas used as bait!
Allah is immortal!
Osman's alps took measure around
the village but it's not enough.
-Around 20 are protecting the village.
-We'll attack together.
No one should survive.
There are Christians living in
this village.
If they accept to live with Turks,
they deserve to die with Turks, Nikola.
Then, let's finish this.
It's better if you stay here and
protect the rear.
You can come to celebrate my
victory when I'm finished.
As you wish, Dukas.
Soldiers! We are moving!
Osman Bey, you don't seem happy
for the victory.
Are you doubting our victory, Osman Bey?
There is something behind this.
They lured us into making a mistake...
and made a sneaky move, I'm afraid.
Let me go!
Commander Dukas!
This victory is yours!
Osman will think that we'll attack...
the Turkish villages around Domaniç.
-I'll transfer this information.
Osman will take the bait.
We'll send soldiers to Domaniç.
A small unit will position there.
We'll take Osman's attention
to there.
-Osman will make his plans for them.
-But the real target will be Kulucahisar.
Great. Great.
I knew that you are a great commander,
Dukas.
-Your plan worked great.
-I must admit.
Athnos has a great part in it.
He managed to deceive Osman
through Leo.
It's still better to not
get so excited.
-What do you mean?
-Osman hasn't moved yet.
Osman made you so afraid, it seems.
I wanted to warn you before
Osman pokes your eyes, Dukas.
Osman and his alps are at Domaniç,
as we planned.
When he finds out, he'll come after me.
It will be his time.
In a great battlefield,
I will end them all.
Do you know what Turks say
in such situations, Dukas?
Inshallah.
Inshallah, Dukas.
What's wrong, Aygül?
Nikola!
Nikola and Dukas attacked villages
near Kulucahisar.
It was a trap, Osman Bey.
It was a trap.
You were right, Osman Bey.
-What's the situation?
-They burned everything.
So many deaths...
They even killed the innocent
Christians and the children...
What are you saying, Aygül?
We hunted...
but...
we became the hunted.
I swear that...
if this trap doesn't sharpen our blades...
if we don't avenge the
lost blood...
may our blades take our lives!
May our blades take our lives!